Inventory of the John R. Bruning Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Digital Photographs and Videorecordings, 2001-2010; 37,364 digital files (486 GB)
  - Afghanistan, Fall 2010; circa 19,700 digital files
    Bruning also captured some other events. In mid-October he flew to FOB Leatherneck and embedded with the 162 Engineers, Oregon National Guard, for its final route clearance mission. Bruning returned to FOB Shank at the end of October. His final images document his departure from Afghanistan on November 1. He went out with 5-158 to FOB Sharona, then to Kandahar, where he said goodbye to the "Big Windy" troops. From there he flew via C-17 to Kuwait, and then to Bilad, Iraq. He caught a medical flight to Ramstein, Germany, then a final C-17 that stopped at Gander, Canada, before landing at McChord AFB, Washington, which he reached five days after leaving FOB Shank.
    - Articles and blog entries
      - Marne Air 3rd CAB backgroud to deployment
    - Nature of the enemy in Logar Province
      Consists of one item, "The Haqqani Network: From Pakistan to Afghanistan," by Jeffrey A. Dressler, in Afghanistan Report 6, published by the Institute for the Study of War
    - Non-Mission in-country photographs
      - 100310 flight line shots on Sunday
      - October 16 2010 with 162 Engineers FOB Leatherneck, 16 October 2010
      - October 17 2010 with 162 Engineers, 17 October 2010
      - October 19 2010 with 162 Engineers brief, 19 October 2010
      - October 26 2010 flight line at sunset, 26 October 2010
    - Numbered missions
      - Mission 00 090510 flight to Shank from Bagram with 1-168, 5 September 2010
      - Mission 01 090610 RPG attack at Tangi, 6 September 2010
      - Mission 02 090710 swing set, 7 September 2010
      - Mission 03 090810 Tangi twice weapons cache, 8 September 2010
      - Mission 04 090910 sling loads at sunrise, 9 September 2010
        - Anson Smith and Captain Hoffman pilots
      - Mission 05 091010 face of the enemy, 10 September 2010
        - Morning air assault John and Joe single engine 173 abb I flew with Eric and Kyle
      - Mission 06 091110 swing wet II, 11 September 2010
        - Morning swing set delivery and afternoon air assault pick up with Apaches
      - Mission 07 091210 John Joe Carmen air assault Tangi slingload twice, 12 September 2010
      - Mission 08 091510 Afghani commando insertion Bob and Anson chalk 2 Eric and Kyle chalk 1, 15 September 2010
      - Mission 09 091610 Joe and Carmen chalk 1 15k, ballots, hinds, 16 September 2010
      - Mission 10 091710 Polish FOB incident, 17 September 2010
      - Mission 11 091810 election day mayhem, 18 September 2010
      - Mission 12 091910 hot LZ Ageristan Bob and Carmen got mortared and zoo on hilltop with ANA and LN, 19 September 2010
      - Mission 13 092210 Shulak air assault and knock and talk, 22 September 2010
      - Mission 14 092310 battalion air assault in Chark Valley flying with LTC Ault, 23 September 2010
      - Mission 15 092610 Bagram Tangi IED and SAF attack and Kyle's act of bravery, 26 September 2010
        - Intel
      - Mission 16 092910 Bob and Anson Ryan, Sully and Jerrik Tangi SAF, 29 September 2010
      - Mission 17 093010 flight to Altimur Czech heavy weapons shoot, 30 September 2010
      - Mission 18 100410 Sorkh Ab Valley with Czechs, 4 October 2010
      - Mission 19 100810 Bob and Anson Sully and Sgt Pollard sunrise over Chinooks ghazni and slingloads plus water to Tangi, 8 October 2010
      - Mission 20 100910 Hoshnapur KLE, 9 October 2010
      - Mission 21 101310 KLE Sorkh Ab Caccas house for tea and lunch, 13 October 2010
      - Mission 22 102010 route cleance to COP Cryptic 162 Engineers, 20 October 2010
      - Mission 23 Blackhearts - Col Ault's grand tour
      - Mission 24 103110 brawler 6 Charkh Valley, 31 October 2010
      - Mission 25 110110 exfil with Big Windy to Kandahar via Sharona, 31 October 2010
        - C17 Kandahar to Kuwait to Bilad to Ramstein to Gandar to McChord
    - Pre-Deployment 1-168 training photos
      - Bravo 1-168 at Ft Hood predeployment training